[Applause]
this week Tyrone visits a local middle
school to promote drug awareness we have
a very special surprise today
let's hear it for Tyrone
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you very much teacher it is truly
an honor and a privilege for me to be
here upon her school or whatever your
school is called today I say it's a
privilege because it's a violation of my
parole to be around children hello
little boys and little girl when I was
little just like you
me and my friends would go home and
smoke marijuana at school do you say
marijuana sometimes dipping embalming
fluid and me and my friends would laugh
and giggle and eat all the cookies
it was terrible terrible I can
definitely say he was the absolute worst
anti-drug speaker in the history of
drugs then I upgraded to a little drug
called acid very inexpensive and of
even young children could have fallen
it's so bad my favorite he basically
told them where and how to buy the stuff
we all know we can sneak into our mama's
room when she's sleeping and take 5 10
min $20 out of purse run on down to
third Street Cassidy bus downtown and
meet Latin American fellow named
Martinez we know that
you know that Martinez stuff you might
be asking well tell you you'd imagine
what you think that is so kind of crime
no take the cap off and snip it
these little ones are ten and eleven
years old
you know like billy-o it smells
delicious
I thought the worst was over I was
mistaken bad children was the first
[Applause]
so that lovely and moving a graphic
story
you welcome teach a I'm not
finished but that's alright
can I get cash for this I've got some
errands to run and I don't think I'm
gonna make the bank thank you kids go
back
[Applause]
Chappelle's Show Chappell Chappell
[Music]